<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-05-02T14:15:20+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Mariopuff</title><subtitle>descroption</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Fulltimate Custom Night: Clickteam Version!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/fcn-to-clickteam/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fulltimate Custom Night: Clickteam Version!" /><published>2025-05-02T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2025-05-02T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/fcn-move-clic</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/fcn-to-clickteam/"><![CDATA[<p>So yesterday I finally showed the game to CzarIsActual, one of FCN’s developers and the playtester. They’re known for beating custom night games’ max modes, and after watching their videos I can say that they are very skilled at custom night games indeed. So I figured I show <i>Fulltimate Custom Night</i> to Czar themself. But we’ve talked, and I realized the limits that FCN currently has. Since the executable version of FCN (downloadable from Game Jolt) is packaged by Turbowarp, or honestly since FCN itself is a Scratch game to begin with, a lot of lag is noticeable due to Scratch really only be made for simple kid projects. And after some testing, it’s true. Every other custom night fangame out there (and even Scott Cawthon’s games!) all use Clickteam as the language of code.</p>

<p>As of now, I’m still pretty darn new to Clickteam, and those icons are driving me insane. I mean, I like the use of icons myself, but this interface is too much to handle. But coding isn’t as simple as sticking blocks together anymore, so I’ll have to get used to coding in Clickteam. If Scott can do it, why can’t I?</p>

<p>So, to celebrate the 80 characters being coded into <i>Fulltimate Custom Night</i>, I, with the assistance of my fellow developers, will remake <i>Fulltimate Custom Night</i> in Clickteam 2.5+ from scratch. This is going to take a lot of time, so maybe it’ll take another year. But let’s hope we can finish this in 6 months or a little more than that.</p>

<p>Oh boy. Here we go again.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[FCN is remaking itself, this time not in Scratch, but in Clickteam... from scratch!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The all-new blog page and system</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/the-all-new-blog-page-and-system/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The all-new blog page and system" /><published>2025-03-30T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2025-03-30T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/blog-announcement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/the-all-new-blog-page-and-system/"><![CDATA[<p>Hello to everyone reading this post! It’s me, Mariopuff and I just finished building my site’s blog system using Jekyll with the help of ChatGPT! (of course it’s AI because I myself am not a coder in any language except for my four-year degree in Scratch game coding) I’ll be using this blog as a news update on my projects, how I feel, what I want to post, my YouTube,… all sorts of random things you could find.</p>

<p>Anyway, enjoy using… MariopuffSite? idk contact me on Discord and DM me some names I should name this site.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blog page and its posts are now available on this site!]]></summary></entry></feed>